John N. Rowe III papers, Inclusive: 1510-1989, undated, Bulk: 1830-1880
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Early Texas Documents, 1801-1989, undated; 2
  - Financial, 1802-1925, undated; 3
    - Financial: Ehring, Robert, Henry Ostermayer, 1858 March 23 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Financial: Eldridge, Joseph C., 1845 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Financial: Ellis, Richard, 1838 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Financial: Elmendorf & Kinsey, 1882 March 15 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Financial: Enterprise Publishing, 1877 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Financial: Ernest, J.R., Kerby McCord, 1861 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Financial: Evans, A.H., Nancy Curl, 1852 November 4 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Financial: Evans, John S., 1841 April (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Financial: Evans, Mark, 1894-1899 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Financial: Everett, Altazira, 1839 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Financial: Everett, W.H., Henrich Beller, 1840 June 20 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Financial: Faison, N.W., 1870 December (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Financial: Fessenden, Isaac, 1853 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Financial: Fessenden, Isaac, 1853 December 26 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Financial: Fessenden, Isaac, C.L. Beissner, 1843 August (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Financial: Firrks, Henry, Jacob Baliman, 1846 October 14 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Financial: First National Bank-Stanton, Foster S. Gamble, 1815 August 13 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Financial: Foster, A., C.H. Randolph, 1862 October (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Financial: Foster, A., G. Hill, 1862 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Financial: Foster, John, 1855 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Financial: Fowst, C., 1862 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Financial: Frederick, M., H.A. Cobb & Company, 1848 March 14 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Financial: French, R.J., 1855-1860 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Financial: Freon, Joseph, 1836 December 31 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Financial: Frosh, Lawrence, Nichols Lang, 1846 January 1 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Financial: Fuller, George S., 1893 August 4 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Financial: Gaines, Nancy A., John Twohig, 1865 February 9 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Financial: Gator, J.H., F.R. Lubbock, 1890 August 4 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Financial: Gayle, A.T., 1837 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Financial: Gelbs, C.C., James H. Cator, 1897 December 24 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Financial: Gengevlar, Jacob, 1838 June 29 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Financial: George Bulter & Brothers, 1852 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Financial: Gerantan, William H., Martha Bostick, 1839 November (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Financial: Gill, Mary M., C.R. Johns, M.H. Royston, M.L. Rolands, 1867 April 4 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Financial: Godin, D., William H. Sandusky, 1846 October 20 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Financial: Godin, E.F., W. Richardson, 1847 May 26 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Financial: Goodbar & Gilliland, Campbell & Strong, H.A. Howell, 1872 March 20 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Financial: Goodnight, Nancy, 1836, 1858 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Financial: Gorman, P.O.-treasury warrant, 1862 January 3 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Financial: Grant, James D., J.D. Drennan, 1863 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Financial: J.D. Grant & H. Robertson Company, C.R. Johns, C.H. Randolph, 1867 October 14 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Financial: Gray, Mitch, 1877 September 7 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Financial: Green, Thomas, 1847 (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Financial: Greenwood, Garrison, 1848 October 26 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Financial: Gresham, Walter, 1877 June (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Financial: Gresham, Walter, Martin Raiden, undated (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Financial: Griffin, John, Mr. Wherley, Peter Martin, 1849 March 19 (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Financial: Griffin, L.H., B.P. Hollingsworth, 1863 April 7 (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - Financial: Groce, L.W. & I.E., 1837 (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - Financial: Guess, Joseph, 1837 (Box 33, Folder 74)
    - Financial: Hall, Edward, 1840-1845 (Box 33, Folder 75)
    - Financial: Hall, William, 1845 (Box 33, Folder 76)
    - Financial: Hamlin, Dr. Buckley & Byrne, undated (Box 33, Folder 77)
    - Financial: Hamilton, M.C., 1844 (Box 33, Folder 78)
    - Financial: Hammer, D. & J.L. Nichols, 1860 November (Box 33, Folder 79)
    - Financial: Hanlon, Felix, 1849 November (Box 33, Folder 80)
    - Financial: Hanlow, Lelend, undated (Box 33, Folder 81)
    - Financial: Hanson, Hans, Boyd Bordner, 1917 December 17 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Financial: Harding, N., 1899 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Harms, E., W.E.H., J.R.K., Santa Rita Mining, 1900 October 8 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Harrell, Garrett, 1844 December (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Harrington, A. Brigham, 1836 September 6 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Harris, B.F., M. Hopkins, 1871 September 7 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Harrison, Henry, Kidder Walker, 1843 April (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Harvey, David, A. Lynn, 1849 January 30 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Financial: Harvey, William, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Harwood, Jim, R. Yeoman, 1859 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Hawkins, Henry, C.N. Randolph, C.R. Johns, J.C. Houghton, 1862 October 4-31 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Hawkins, William J., 1838 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Financial: Hayes, J.M., 1881 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Heath, E.M., C.N. Randolph, George L. Durham, 1861 March 14 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Financial: Helmiller, F., 1837 November 24 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Hemsworth, Thomas, John S. Evans, 1840 February 5 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Henry Shelden & Company, C.H. & W. Raquet, 1853 October 25 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Henshaw, Benjamin, [illegible] Pomeroy, 1789 December 23 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Hershfeld, H., C.N. Johns, 1862 April 2 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Hewitt, Law. S., Charles Swason, James B. Shaw, 1844 October 19 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Hicks, C.B., Dr. B.S. Johnson, C.N. Randolph, C.N. Johns, 1864 March 15 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Hill, Ben P., James H. Raymond, 1850 August 25 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Hill, G.W., 1844 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Hill, N.S., E.L. Green, Oscar Farish, 1853 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Financial: Himes, S.P., 1865 December 19 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Financial: Hobson, John, 1837 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Financial: Hodges, Nancy L., Nancy L. O’Barr, 1849 April (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Financial: Hoffman, Charles, Schooner Flor Del Mar, P. McLaughlin & Company, 1839 January 26 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Financial: Holbun, Hugh, Joseph P. Burger, 1844 July 1 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Financial: Home, William, R. Daily, 1840 October (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Financial: Hood, Joseph L., undated (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Financial: Hooper, L.E., John Pendleton, 1853 August 5 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Financial: Hooreth, E.W., 1839 March 1 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Financial: Hornberg, Henry, William P. Ballinger & Thomas Jack, 1856 May 21 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Financial: Hotchkiss, Archibald, C.W. Hotchkiss, 1847 August 27 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Financial: Hotchkiss, Captain, Charles Chevaillier, 1839 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Financial: Howell, Herbert, A.F. James, Snyder & James, 1847 February (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Financial: Hoya, Charles, M.G. Ratcliff, 1906 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Financial: Hubbell, Nathan, Barnard Bee, 1837 December 2 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Financial: Huchting, C.C., C.L. Brauer & Son, Kauffman & Klaener, 1855 September 8 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Financial: Hudson, L.S., C.H. Randolph, C.N. Randolph, C.R. Johns, 1864 September 21 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Financial: Huff, T.A., 1925 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Financial: Hunber, W.H., Kerby McCord, 1861 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Financial: Hutchisson, Robert, 1837 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Financial: Hyde, Prentiss, 1842 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Financial: The Hydeville Company, 1862 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Financial: Hyman, P.H., Carpenter, 1872 September 24 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Financial: Illies, John H., William R. Smith, 1852 January 5 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - Financial: Illingworth, J.O., 1863 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Financial: Irvin, John G., James H. Cator, 1898 February 15 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Financial: James, Alfred F., J.N. Beaumont, 1847 January 1 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - Financial: James, Alfred F., Smythe & Lynn, 1847 May (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Financial: Jamison, Isaac, Gail Borden, Jr., 1836 December 22 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Financial: Jay, Josiah, M.B. Gidding, 1837 August 25 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Financial: Johns, N., J. Crosby, 1862 October 8 (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Financial: Johnson, L.S., 1842 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Financial: L.F. Johnson & Company, 1860 August 10 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Financial: Johnson, Captain William., Isaac G. Williams, 1840 April (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Financial: Jones, B., 1836 (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Financial: Jones, Churchill, 1855 January 1 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Financial: Jones, J.H., 1904 December 1 (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Financial: Jones, J.W., Arthur Land, 1898 May 9 (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Financial: Jones, Nicholas, 1874 August (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Financial: Jones, Simon L., Schooner Emblem, 1839 June 10 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - Financial: Jones, Simon L., Samuel B. Shaw, 1853 June 16 (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Financial: Jones, William Jefferson, Samuel B. Shaw, Charles Mason, H. Jack, William H. Dangerfield, 1842 December 27 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Financial: Jordan, Christian, Mrs. Westerlage, 1858 November 8 (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Financial: Julizeos, Michael, Joseph Paskiwitch (Pascovitch), undated (Box 34, Folder 68)
    - Financial: Juss & Norman, John R. Mills, 1839 September 1 (Box 34, Folder 69)
    - Financial: Katherman, W.J., James H. Cator, 1900 December 10 (Box 34, Folder 70)
    - Financial: Kauffman & Klaener, Commercial Restaurant, 1853 September 15 (Box 34, Folder 71)
    - Financial: Kellogg, S.G., 1837 (Box 34, Folder 72)
    - Financial: Kelly, John W., 1861 (Box 34, Folder 73)
    - Financial: Kelso, O.N.P., A. & C. Brown Company, C.R. Johns, C.N. Randolph, 1862 October 16 (Box 34, Folder 74)
    - Financial: Kennedy, Hugh, A. Edgar, 1842 October 2 (Box 34, Folder 75)
    - Financial: Kesler, Charles, George W. Smith, 1859 (Box 34, Folder 76)
    - Financial: Kesler, Henry, 1842 (Box 34, Folder 77)
    - Financial: King, Hardy, 1837 (Box 34, Folder 78)
    - Financial: King, John, Arthur Land, 1898 May 9 (Box 34, Folder 79)
    - Financial: Kinion, Alfred, 1838 (Box 34, Folder 80)
    - Financial: Kirchhoffer & Woodward, R. & D.G. Mills, 1854 February 20 (Box 34, Folder 81)
    - Financial: Kirkland, P., 1842 December 31 (Box 34, Folder 82)
    - Financial: Kirkland, Stephen, Robert D. Johnson, 1840 January 1 (Box 34, Folder 83)
    - Financial: Kirkland, Stephen, Steamboat Dayton, 1841 April 7 (Box 34, Folder 84)
    - Financial: Korn, Louis, R.W. Riley, 1861 (Box 34, Folder 85)
    - Financial: Kramer, B., Briggs O. Garde, N.B. Yard, 1854 May (Box 34, Folder 86)
    - Financial: Kramer, B, 1855 February 28 (Box 34, Folder 87)
    - Financial: Kramer, M., Adolph Flake, 1854 April 22 (Box 34, Folder 88)
    - Financial: Krim, Daniel, Rains and Downing, 1842 December 31 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Financial: Krim & Sherwood, William Nettles, 1842 December 10 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Krim, Daniel W., 1842 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Krim, Daniel W. (in pieces), 1842 October (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Kuykendall, Abram, 1848 June 27 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Kuykendall, Robert H., 1837 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Lamb, Martha Bostick, 1858 November 28 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Lambert, John, 1856 April 4 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Financial: Lambert, John, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Lambeth, William M., P.W. Grayson, 1837 January 15 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Landers, L.B., D.P. Flint, Veroni & Moore, 1850 January 24 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Lang, Michael, John Lang, 1845 January 11 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Financial: Larson, A.J., 1912 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Laughlin & Avery, Harrison Atwood, 1850 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Financial: Lawrence, George F., P.R. Edwards, 1840 June 1 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Lee, Theodore S., 1837 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Leggin & Roberts, Deck & Phillips, 1839 November 19 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Financial: LeGrand, Alexander, 1844 March 12 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Lellens, William, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Lender, John, 1849 June 4 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Lender, John, 1849 July 11 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Lender, John, 1849 August 1 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Lender, John H., Fredrich Vornbaumen, John P. Wirtz, 1850 August (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Lender, John H., Frederich Vordenbaumen, 1851 August 20 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Financial: Lender, John H., Frederich Meyer, 1852 August 12 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Financial: Level, N.H., 1861 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Financial: Lewis, C. (Saul)-Caravansary, 1841 May (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Financial: Lewis, A.N., J.W. McMahan, 1874 January 10 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Financial: Lewis, A.N., J.W. McMahan, 1874 February 1 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Financial: Lewis, Allen, 1883 August 4 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Financial: Lewis, H.K., John W. McMahan, undated (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Financial: Lewis, Hattie K., Fannie McMahan, 1877 July 18 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Financial: Lewis, John H., [illegible] Oakey, 1841 October 2 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Financial: Lewis, M.P., 1836 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Financial: Lewis, William W., undated (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Financial: Linden, J.H., Frederich Vandenbaumen, James Cronican, 1850 October 21 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Financial: Lise, Sephring, 1837 August 15 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Financial: Long, James M., 1845 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Financial: Lost, A.N., W.T. Sharp, J.S. Robinson, 1889 December 30 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Financial: Louis, Francis D., David Davis, 1839 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Financial: Love, James, 1837 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Financial: Lucas, John H., 1846 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Financial: Luce, W.R., 1859 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Financial: Lynch, Elisha O., William B. Harmon, 1851 March 19 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Financial: Lynch, George P., James Walton, 1848 February 2 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Financial: Maas, Samuel, Schooner Fradue, 1855 April 13 (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Financial: Magill, J.H., 1857 (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Financial: Magill, J.H., undated (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - Financial: Magill, John H., A.F. Jones, 1857 June 21 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Financial: Magill, Paul P. Jr., C.H. Randolph, Clement R. Jones, E. Sampson, 1859 November 23 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Financial: Mariner, Charles, Charles Mason, Samuel B. Shaw, 1844 February (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Financial: Martic, Peter, 1849 August (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Financial: Martic, Peter, undated (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Financial: Martin, J.L., 1849 (Box 35, Folder 54)
    - Financial: Marvin, Seth, 1839 (Box 35, Folder 55)
    - Financial: Mason, Charles, George W. Poe, 1839 December 13 (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Financial: Mason, Charles, Ebenezer Allen, 1846 January 3 (Box 35, Folder 57)
    - Financial: Mason, J.J., 1860 (Box 35, Folder 58)
    - Financial: Mathews, J.P. (Estate), 1867-1871 (Box 35, Folder 59)
    - Financial: Maume, Matthew, A. Pickett, 1862 August 26 (Box 35, Folder 60)
    - Financial: Maunir Estate, J.P. Nash, 1862 September 9 (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - Financial: Maurice, H.P., John Twoling & Company Bankers, 1874 April (Box 35, Folder 62)
    - Financial: Maybury, M.V., 1865-1867 (Box 35, Folder 63)
    - Financial: Mayers, M., William H. Mayers, [illegible] January 5 (Box 35, Folder 64)
    - Financial: McCarthy, Charles L., Trinity Church, 1854 January 14 (Box 35, Folder 65)
    - Financial: McCleaster, Hiram B., Mordecai Primrose, 1845 October 13 (Box 35, Folder 66)
    - Financial: McCord, Kerby, Q.G. New, 1861 (Box 35, Folder 67)
    - Financial: McCracklin, J.L., 1844 November 25 (Box 35, Folder 68)
    - Financial: McCullough, Allen, Phihllip & Deck, 1839 July 6 (Box 35, Folder 69)
    - Financial: McCullough, William H., 1850 April 29 (Box 35, Folder 70)
    - Financial: McDermit, John, 1837 (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - Financial: McGahry, James S., 1838 (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - Financial: McGray, J.H., S. Vanhook, James Hamilton, John H. Hamilton, W.W. Packs, 1857 September 10 (Box 35, Folder 73)
    - Financial: McKenzie, John, J.P. McKinney, 1839 May 5 (Box 35, Folder 74)
    - Financial: McKinney & Williams, Martha Scott, David Scott, 1840 September (Box 35, Folder 75)
    - Financial: McLaughlin, Philip, Phillip & Norton, undated (Box 35, Folder 76)
    - Financial: McLean, Ephraim, Charles Mason, 1845 February 5 (Box 35, Folder 77)
    - Financial: McLean, Joseph S., 1837 June 16 (Box 35, Folder 78)
    - Financial: McMahon, Mrs. F.H., 1873 September 1 (Box 35, Folder 79)
    - Financial: McMahan, John W., Fannie McMahan, Hattie Lewis, undated (Box 35, Folder 80)
    - Financial: McMahan, J.W., Hattie Lewis, Fannie McMahan, 1877 May (Box 35, Folder 81)
    - Financial: McMahan, John W., Frances McMahan, 1877 July-November (Box 35, Folder 82)
    - Financial: McMillen, J.H., 1853 (Box 35, Folder 83)
    - Financial: McMillan, J.H., 1854 February 2, 18 (Box 35, Folder 84)
    - Financial: McMillan, J.H., 1854 February 27 (Box 35, Folder 85)
    - Financial: McNeal, Charles B, 1836 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Financial: Memphis, El Paso and Pacific Rail-Road, 1860s (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Financial: Menard, P.J., Samuel Whiting, 1838 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Financial: Menard, Peter J., J.A. Settle, 1840 January 26 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Financial: Merewater, M.O., 1837 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Financial: Merle, C.A., Edmond Andrews, James P. McKinny, E.A. Rhodes, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Financial: Messer, John W., C.N. Randolph, Clement R. Johns, 1860 July 19 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Financial: Meyes, Horatio, 1837 June 15 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Financial: Miles, George-Town of Swartout, Texas, circa 1838 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Miles, James, G. Huff & Son, 1832-1834, 1838 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Financial: Miller, C.H., 1850 September 1 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Financial: Miller, Daniel, 1869 December 31 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Financial: Miller, Robert L., 1865 September 5 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Miller, S.K., C.R. Johns & Company, 1870 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Financial: Mills, R., 1851 December 31 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Financial: Mills, R. & D.G., B.D. Wade, 1854 August 31 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Financial: Mills, Robert & Company, 1837 September 1 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Financial: Mills, R. & D.G., 1855 June 8 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Financial: Millson, Sarah, 1838 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Financial: Millspaugh, Benjamin, 1837 June 15 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Financial: Mitchell, Ele., J.H. Raymond, George L. Durham, James B. Shaw, 1852 February 18 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Financial: Moorback, George, Bernard Crowe, undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Financial: Moore, Charles D., 1841-1846 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Financial: Moore, Charles H., 1898 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Financial: Moore, James W., Lent M. Hitchcock, J.M. Allen, 1845 June 31 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Financial: Moore, James W., Frankland & Company, 1842 March 12 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Financial: Morgan, Antonio, John Prevara, undated (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Financial: Morland, Isaac N., George W. Poe, 1836 October 28 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Financial: Morris & Blair, 1861-1862 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Financial: Morris, William, John Grant, 1839 December 28 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Financial: Morrison, C.L., 1837 September 11 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Financial: Moses & Kelley, 1874 March 23 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Financial: Mulkey, James D., C.N. Randolph, Clements R. Johns, Edward Clark, Allen W. Nabeu, 1860 December 11 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Financial: Mullen, John, 1838 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Financial: Munson, David, Beason [illegible], George Morris, William Robertson, 1839 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Financial: Munson, Lent Hitchcock, 1845 April 16 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Financial: Murray, Captain George, Ferdinand Flake, Schooner Eglantine, 1850 May 1 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Financial: Myers, A., 1857 January 30 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Financial: Nabors, B.F., Jackson Smith, 1845 June 9 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Financial: National Exchange Hotel Company, 1860s (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Financial: Naval Payment Certificates-Texas, 1841 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Financial: Neal, John, Schooner Henry, P. McLaughlin & Company, 1837 June 29 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - Financial: Neal, W.G., 1862 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Financial: Neill, James C., George W. Poe, 1836 October 6 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Financial: Nelson, Daniel S., 1837 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Financial: Newton, Mary, Jacob Sasse, A. Lewis & Company, 1846 April (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Financial: Newton, Mary, Jacob Sasse, A. Lewis & Company, 1846 August (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Financial: Newton, Warren, 1889 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Financial: Nichols, E.B., C.H. Randolph, 1863 May 23 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Financial: Nichols, George H., 1837 (Box 36, Folder 50)
    - Financial: Nichols, George M., 1841 September (Box 36, Folder 51)
    - Financial: Nichols, Mrs. M.E., Hattie Lewis, John W. McMahan, 1877 April 30 (Box 36, Folder 52)
    - Financial: Nichols, William B., P. McLaughlin, Robert D. Johnson, 1840 January 3 (Box 36, Folder 53)
    - Financial: Nicholson, M.H., 1842 (Box 36, Folder 54)
    - Financial: Nixon, George A., 1836 (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - Financial: Nixon, Neal, 1836 (Box 36, Folder 56)
    - Financial: Nolan, John, 1838 (Box 36, Folder 57)
    - Financial: Norrell, William, 1836 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Financial: Norwood, Nathaniel, John H. Sterritt, 1840 September 5 (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Financial: Oakey, S.W., William Bryan, undated (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Financial: Oban, John, Nancy L. Hodges, 1850 October (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Financial: Occupation Taxes Collected in the Third Quarter, Colorado County, 1875 (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Financial: O’Brian, John, Dennis Compion, 1840 (Box 36, Folder 63)
    - Financial: O’Brian, John, Denis Compion, 1840 September 12 (Box 36, Folder 64)
    - Financial: Ogden, F.M., 1844 (Box 36, Folder 65)
    - Financial: O’Hannelly, [illegible], 1841 (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Financial: Oldham, T.C., 1837 (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - Financial: O’Rourke, James, Crimm & Sherwood, 1842 November 19 (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Financial: Oliver, N.-Caravansary, 1841 May (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - Financial: Owens, J.S., D. Krimm, 1840 March 26 (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - Financial: Pace, Wesley W., R. Barr, R.D. Johnson, 1839 August 28 (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - Financial: Pace, Wesley W., John D. Chamberlain, 1838 September 1 (Box 36, Folder 72)
    - Financial: Pantallion, Benard, 1839 January 30 (Box 36, Folder 73)
    - Financial: Parish, R.L., H.R. McCaslin, 1888 November 12 (Box 36, Folder 74)
    - Financial: Parke, Ellen, 1852 August 20 (Box 36, Folder 75)
    - Financial: Park, Ellen, 1850 August 21 (Box 36, Folder 76)
    - Financial: Parke, E., 1851 April (Box 36, Folder 77)
    - Financial: Parker, G.H.-Caravansary, 1841 May-June (Box 36, Folder 78)
    - Financial: Parker, Hannah, Allen & McCullough, 1839 August 17 (Box 36, Folder 79)
    - Financial: Parkerton, Joseph, 1841 December (Box 36, Folder 80)